<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TOBOR A TON MA I</title>
    <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TOBOR A TON MA I</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aswanipranjal.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep inside the tunnel</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-2/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so in week 2, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some good challenges to overcome. I was given 3 tasks this week:
 To cleanup esquery.py file. This file is the primary file to create elasticsearch DSL queries which are sent to elasticsearch to get the required results. To create from scratch, a new notebook which queries elasticsearch enriched indices and calculates the metrics. To think about structure of new classes and functions that can be created for the metrics as the old classes are cumbersome to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insert coin to begin</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-1/</guid>
      <description>This week was interesting! I read the manuscripts base code and played with a lot of functions to learn how they work. It was fun because after being stuck on a few functions and classes, I finally understood that I should burn my laptop, giveup and go home. Good bye!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/communitybonding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/communitybonding/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post describing what I have being doing since the starting of the community boding period. There will be one post every wednesday, starting next week, describing what I did the previous week and having links to all the necessary resources to track the project.
Community Bonding (April 23rd - May 10th) The community bonding period lasts from 23rd April - 13th April. During this time, I had to understand how the community works and how I should participate in the discussions that happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC Prep</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/gsoc-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/gsoc-prep/</guid>
      <description>Before the orgs were announced Since I enrolled into Engineering back in 2014, I wanted to participate in GSoC. I tried to apply in 2016 and 2017 but didn&amp;rsquo;t get in. This is my final year of Engineering and this year I meant business.
I was interning at Network Intelligence India (1) Pvt. Ltd. when the program schedule for 2018 was announced. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a concrete plan in mind at that time but I knew that I wanted to apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Pranjal</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! I am Pranjal Aswani and I program computers for a living.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been selected in Google Summer of Code-18 under the CHAOSS
I am interested in Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence and currently I am looking for remote opportunities.
Resume
Contact: email</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>