<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gsoc 18 on TOBOR A TON MA I</title>
    <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/tags/gsoc-18/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gsoc 18 on TOBOR A TON MA I</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 12:06:57 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aswanipranjal.github.io/tags/gsoc-18/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week-11</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 12:06:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-11/</guid>
      <description>If you have a good testing infrastructure, you can do anything with your code. Everything becomes easy because you know that as long as the tests are passing, everything is A-Okay. The only downside is that testing is hard, man.
Welcome to Google Summer of Code-18: Week-11.
In Brief Task-5 [Almost Done (still..)]: Task: Try to figure out how to calculate the metrics which depend on Pull Requests Comment data and any other that are remaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All hands on deck!</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 08:54:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-10/</guid>
      <description>I am very happy to inform y&amp;rsquo;all that I&amp;rsquo;ve passed my second evaluation. Jesus and Valerio helped me a ton in this phase so I&amp;rsquo;d like to thank them. I&amp;rsquo;d also like to thank all of the CHAOSS community for their active participation in defining and discussing the details of the remaining metrics.
Aaaaaaaaaand we are in the final phase of GSoC. This is now or never people!! Welcome to Google Summer of Code-18 Week-10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you are happy that you are growing clap your hands!!</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 12:49:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-9/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to get into Stoicism and last night I read this quote:
“Nothing is slower than the true birth of a man.”  Well, this week I understand perfectly what it means.
Hello and welcome to Week-9 of Google Summer of Code!
In Brief Last week, we left off with the following tasks.
Task-2 [Under Progress]: Try to participate in the discussions regarding GMD and other metrics (Task-2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 07:04:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-8/</guid>
      <description>HELLO!!
In this week, I did some experiments and got some good results. Welcome to Week-8 of Google Summer of Code!
In Brief Task-2 [Under Discussion]:  Open issues for unclear metrics  As last week, this week too the Task-2 is being discussed in the mailing lists.
Task-3 [Almost Done]:  Create new chainable functions and classes to calcualte the metrics
 I know, Almost Done is a weird tag, but it&amp;rsquo;s true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pause, reflect and Plan ahead!</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 06:51:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-7/</guid>
      <description>Hey all! I am sorry for been gone for so long.
Welcome to Week-7 of Google Summer of Code. First of all, I&amp;rsquo;d like to thank my mentors: Jesus and Valerio for passing me in the first evaluations! I am very happy about it. They&amp;rsquo;ve been really great and supportive throughout and I&amp;rsquo;d like to Thank them for that.
Since I skipped the last week, this post might be a little longer than usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come with me.. and you&#39;ll be.. in a world of visualizations, tests and documentation </title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 08:14:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-5/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: Bold text apart from headings are links to files/images/notebooks. Kindly click on them for better explainations.
This week (WEEK 5) in Manuscripts: A quest for better reporting of your projects, we will look at some visualizations depecting the various Metrics. We will also see a lot of tests and some documentation describing the new_functions created.
In-Brief Introduction to the week. We&amp;rsquo;ll look at some tasks and their status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do you Debug? I use a lot of *print* statements and patience</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 16:12:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-4/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Week 4 of Google Summer of Code. It said in one of the emails from Google, that time will move pretty fast. Yep, 4 weeks over!
Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the tasks to be completed in this week.
Brief introduction TASK-1: I created the last PR which completes the migration of manuscripts to elasticsearch_dsl module. The main purpose of this PR was to change esquery.py and metrics.py so that the functions do not directly query elasticsearch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A week full of hiccups</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 23:43:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-3/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to the third week of Google Summer of Code. I hit a couple of speed bumps this week.
Highlights: Task-1: Complete cleaning esquery.py file, add tests and make the whole manuscripts project use elasticsearch_dsl.py module.
Progress: I was able to complete writing tests for esquery.py and make the comments more detailed. The changes can be found here. This is the part of the previous PR that I made in the previous week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep inside the tunnel</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-2/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so in week 2, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some good challenges to overcome. I was given 3 tasks this week:
 To cleanup esquery.py file. This file is the primary file to create elasticsearch DSL queries which are sent to elasticsearch to get the required results. To create from scratch, a new notebook which queries elasticsearch enriched indices and calculates the metrics. To think about structure of new classes and functions that can be created for the metrics as the old classes are cumbersome to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insert coin to begin</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-1/</guid>
      <description>This week was interesting! I read the manuscripts base code and played with a lot of functions to learn how they work. It was fun because after being stuck on a few functions and classes, I finally understood that I should burn my laptop, giveup and go home. Good bye!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/communitybonding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/communitybonding/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post describing what I have being doing since the starting of the community boding period. There will be one post every wednesday, starting next week, describing what I did the previous week and having links to all the necessary resources to track the project.
Community Bonding (April 23rd - May 10th) The community bonding period lasts from 23rd April - 13th April. During this time, I had to understand how the community works and how I should participate in the discussions that happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC Prep</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/gsoc-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/gsoc-prep/</guid>
      <description>Before the orgs were announced Since I enrolled into Engineering back in 2014, I wanted to participate in GSoC. I tried to apply in 2016 and 2017 but didn&amp;rsquo;t get in. This is my final year of Engineering and this year I meant business.
I was interning at Network Intelligence India (1) Pvt. Ltd. when the program schedule for 2018 was announced. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a concrete plan in mind at that time but I knew that I wanted to apply.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>