<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TOBOR A TON MA I</title>
    <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TOBOR A TON MA I</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 14:58:34 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>init: start code</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 14:58:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/week-1/</guid>
      <description>This week was interesting! I read the manuscripts base code and played with a lot of functions to learn how they work. It was fun because after being stuck on a few functions and classes, I finally understood that I should burn my laptop, giveup and go home.
Just kidding! I was actually able to add</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/communitybonding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/communitybonding/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post describing what I have being doing since the starting of the community boding period. There will be one post every wednesday, starting next week, describing what I did the previous week and having links to all the necessary resources to track the project.
Community Bonding (April 23rd - May 10th) The community bonding period lasts from 23rd April - 13th April. During this time, I had to understand how the community works and how I should participate in the discussions that happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSoC Prep</title>
      <link>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/gsoc-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswanipranjal.github.io/posts/gsoc-prep/</guid>
      <description>Before the orgs were announced Since I enrolled into Engineering back in 2014, I wanted to participate in GSoC. I tried to apply in 2016 and 2017 but didn&amp;rsquo;t get in. This is my final year of Engineering and this year I meant business.
I was interning at Network Intelligence India (1) Pvt. Ltd. when the program schedule for 2018 was announced. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a concrete plan in mind at that time but I knew that I wanted to apply.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>